Guide to the Gerhard Casper, President of Stanford University, Papers SC0672
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- President's records, 1999-2000; Accession ARCH-2002-228
  - President's Office, AD 4.0 (Box 3)
  - Presidential Lecture Symposium Human & Arts (PLSHA), 9/23/99 - 8/31/00; AD 4.2 (Box 3)
  - President's House, Staff, Car, AD 4.7 (Box 3)
  - University Cabinet, AD 4.13 (Box 3)
  - General Correspondences, 1/6/00 - 7/24/00; AD 4.20 (Box 3)
  - News Clippings, AD 4.20.1 (Box 3)
  - Condolence Letters, AD 4.20.2 (Box 3)
  - Congratulatory Letters, 9/17/99 - 7/17/00; AD 4.20.3 (Box 3)
  - Letters of Appreciation, 9/2/98 - 8/1/00; AD 4.20.4/1 (Box 3)
  - Invitations, 7/19/00 - 9/5/00; AD 4.20.4/2 (Box 3)
  - Invitations, 3/14/00 - 6/5/00 (Box 3)
  - Invitations, 12/10/99 - 2/28/00 (Box 3)
  - Invitations, 9/21/99 - 12/6/99 (Box 3)
  - Casper's Resignation, AD 4.20.4/3 (Box 3)
  - Nonsense, 9/10/99 - 8/28/00; AD 4.20.5 (Box 3)
  - Routine Recommendation Letters (search letters), 9/14/99 - 7/21/00; AD 4.20.6 (Box 3)
  - Recommendations Letters (Students), 11/27/99 - 3/15/00; AD 4.20.6/1 (Box 3)
  - Complaint Letters, 10/1/99 - 7/12/00; AD 4.20.7 (Box 3)
  - Solicitation Letters (General), 12/21/99 - 2/29/00; AD 4.20.8 (Box 3)
  - Solicitation Letters (General), 10/18/99 - 12/16/99\ (Box 3)
  - Solicitation Letters (General), 9/7/99 - 10/18/99 (Box 3)
  - University Communications, 9/5/99 - 8/17/00; AD 4.22 (Box 4)
  - Office of Campus Relations, 9/21/99 - 6/22/00; AD 6 (Box 4)
  - Admissions, AD 8.1 (Box 4)
  - Student Affairs, Dean of, 9/8/99 - 8/23/00; AD 8.8 (Box 4)
  - Cowell Student Health Center, AD 8.9 (Box 4)
  - Stanford in Washington D.C., AD 8.10.1 (Box 4)
  - Overseas Studies Programs, 9/16/99 - 8/3/00; AD 8.11 (Box 4)
  - Financial Aid, AD 8.12 (Box 4)
  - Faculty, Staff, Emeriti, Housing, 1/30/00 - 8/3/00; AD 8.18 (Box 4)
  - Faculty, Staff, Emeriti, Housing, 9/28/99 - 1/11/00 (Box 4)
  - Hanna-Honeycomb House, AD 8.18.2 (Box 4)
  - Lake House, AD 8.18.3 (Box 4)
  - Buck Estate, AD 8.18.4 (Box 4)
  - Housing/Dining Services-Students, AD 8.18.11 (Box 4)
  - Residential Education, 9/3/99 - 7/13/00; AD 8.18.13 (Box 4)
  - Registrar - Bursar, 9/19/99 - 8/14/00; AD 8.21 (Box 4)
  - Multi-Cultural Development, AD 9.6 (Box 4)
  - Affirmative Action, Student, AD 9.6.3 (Box 4)
  - Employee and Personnel Relations, 10/12/99 - 8/10/00; AD 10 (Box 4)
  - Employment Inquiries/Requests, AD 10.1 (Box 4)
  - Committee for Art, AD 10.7.4 (Box 4)
  - United Stanford Employees (USE), AD 10.7.8 (Box 4)
  - Grievances - Student, AD 10.8.10/3 (Box 4)
  - Retirement, AD 10.8.17 (Box 4)
  - Salaries, AD 10.8.19 (Box 4)
  - Operations and Maintenance, AD 11.4 (Box 4)
  - Environmental Safety Facility, AD 11.4.1 (Box 4)
  - Police Services/Campus Security, AD 11.6 (Box 4)
  - Stanford Events, 9/13/99 - 5/30/00; AD 11.7.5/1 (Box 4)
  - Lively Arts at Stanford, 10/4/99 - 8/31/00; AD 11.7.5/2 (Box 4)
  - Freshmen Orientation, AD 11.7.7 (Box 4)
  - Media - All Forms - External, 9/1/99 - 7/14/00; AD 11.8 (Box 4)
  - Stanford University Press, 9/29/99 - 6/29/00; AD 11.8.9 (Box 4)
  - Surveys, Studies, Questionnaires, 9/1/99 - 7/18/00; AD 11.8.10 (Box 4)
  - Media, Internal, 9/10/99 - 8/28/00; AD 11.8.11 (Box 4)
  - Business and Finance, 9/10/99 - 7/24/00; AD 12.2 (Box 4)
  - Administrative Resources, 9/8/99 - 7/18/00; AD 12.2/3 (Box 4)
  - Stanford Management Company, 9/22/99 - 8/18/00; AD 12.3 (Box 4)
  - Internal Auditing, AD 12.4 (Box 4)
  - Budget (Budget Group), AD 12.5 (Box 4)
  - Tuition, AD 12.5.4 (Box 4)
  - Institutional Planning: Geoff Cox, AD 12.6 (Box 4)
  - Insurance, Risk Management, AD 12.8 (Box 4)
  - Vice President for Development, AD 12.10 (Box 4)
  - Office of Development, AD 12.10.1 (Box 4)
  - President Discretionary Allocation, AD 12.10.2 (Box 4)
  - Student Fund Raising, AD 12.10.2/1 (Box 4)
  - President's Fund, AD 12.10.2/2 (Box 4)
  - The Stanford Fund, AD 12.10.2/3 (Box 4)
  - Matching Gifts, AD 12.10.2/4 (Box 4)
  - Development, Events, AD 12.10.2/5 (Box 4)
  - Donor Relations, AD 12.10.2/7 (Box 4)
  - Asian Relations, General, 1/26/00 - 8/23/00; AD 12.10.2/9 (Box 4)
  - Asian Relations, General, 9/15/99 - 1/18/00 (Box 4)
  - Land and Buildings, General catch all, 5/28/00 - 8/25/00; AD 12.14 (Box 5)
  - Land and Buildings, General catch all, 3/10/00 - 5/19/00 (Box 5)
  - Land and Buildings, General catch all, 9/18/99 - 3/13/00 (Box 5)
  - Housing, Land and Building Issues, AD 12.14.1 (Box 5)
  - Art Gallery & Museums, 12/3/99 (1 Doc(); AD 12.14.7/1 (Box 5)
  - Bookstore, Stanford, AD 12.14.7/5 (Box 5)
  - Facilities / Planning / Univ. Architect, 9/1/99 - 8/15/00; AD 12.14.7/29 (Box 5)
  - Faculty Club, 10/22/98 only; AD 12.14.7/30 (Box 5)
  - Jasper Ridge Biological Experimental Area (space), AD 12.14.7/43 (Box 5)
  - Memorial Church, 9/18/98 - 6/20/99; AD 12.14.7/50 (Box 5)
  - Parking/Transportation, 9/18/98 - 6/20/100; AD 12.14.7/53 (Box 5)
  - Tressider Memorial Union (TMU), 9/18/98 - 6/20/101; AD 12.14.7/64 (Box 5)
  - Visitors to campus, 9/18/98 - 6/20/102; AD 13.10 (Box 5)
  - Conferences, Misc., 2/22/00 - 8/8/00; AD 13.10.1 (Box 5)
  - Industrial Relations, 10/27/98 - 4/22/99; AD 15 (Box 5)
  - Alumni Relations, 9/2/99 - 4/3/00; AL 1 (Box 5)
  - Parent's Club (formerly known as "Mother's Club"), AL 1.1/1 (Box 5)
  - Alumni Correspondence (General - Not Parent/Student), 4/4/00 - 8/30/00; AL 1.3 (Box 5)
  - Alumni Correspondence (General - Not Parent/Student), 10/23/99 - 4/5/00 (Box 5)
  - Alumni Correspondence (General - Not Parent/Student), 9/3/99 - 10/21/99 (Box 5)
  - Alumni Letter Campaign/ Stanford Magazine Classnote, 5/4/00 - 8/16/00; AL 1.3.1 (Box 5)
  - Annual Graduate Mailing, AL 1.4 (Box 5)
  - Alumni Conference/Homecoming, AL 1.7 (Box 5)
  - Alumni Association, AL 3 (Box 5)
  - SAA - 2000 (Stanford Alumni Association), AL 3.1 (Box 5)
  - Alumni Giving (OOD), AL 5 (Box 5)
  - Board of Trustees, 9/1/99 - 7/13/00; B 1 (Box 5)
  - Board of Trustees Appointments, B 12 (Box 5)
  - Board of Trustees Committees, 9/20/99 - 8/3/00; B 14 (Box 5)
  - Trustee Committee on Land & Use Building Campus Plng, B 14.6 (Box 5)
  - Academic Council, C 1 (Box 5)
  - Academic Council - Senate, 5/8/00 - 6/8/00; C 2 (Box 5)
  - Academic Council - Senate, 4/10/00 - 1/29/00; C2 (Box 6)
  - Academic Council - Senate, 1/5/00 - 4/10/00 (Box 6)
  - Academic Council - Senate, 9/27/99 - 1/4/00 (Box 6)
  - Academic Council - Advisory Board, 12/1/99 - 8/22/00; C 3 (Box 6)
  - Academic Council - Steering Committee - STC, C 4.1 (Box 6)
  - Commission on Technology in Teaching and Learning, C 5.7.2 (Box 6)
  - University Committees, C 6 (Box 6)
  - Committee of Fifteen, C 6.1 (Box 6)
  - General Gov't Info., 1/10/00 - 7/14/00; G 1 (Box 6)
  - Performing Arts Center - [Government Misc.], G1 PAC (Box 6)
  - California State Government, G 1.2 (Box 6)
  - Environmental Protection Agency, G 2.3 (Box 6)
  - U.S. Governmental Relations, 9/2/99 - 8/24/00; G 3 (Box 6)
  - Department of Defense (DoD), G 3.7 (Box 6)
  - Department of Energy (DoE), G 3.7.2 (Box 6)
  - National Aeronautics & Space Administration (NASA), G 3.7.4 (Box 6)
  - Health & Human Services, Office of Civil Rights, G 3.8.1 (Box 6)
  - National Institutes of Health (NIH), G 3.8.2 (Box 6)
  - Department of Education, U.S. (USDE), G 3.8.3 (Box 6)
  - Internal Revenue Service (IRS), G 3.18.1 (Box 6)
  - NSF - National Science Foundation, 5/19/00 - 18/28/00; G 3.19 (Box 6)
  - NSF - National Science Foundation, 9/17/99 - 5/18/00 (Box 6)
  - NSF - National Science Foundation, 9/1/1999 (1 Doc) (Box 6)
  - Local Government / Local Business, 9/1/99 - 7/13/00; G 4 (Box 6)
  - Foreign Government Relations, misc., 9/20/99 - 7/18/00; G 5 (Box 6)
  - CA Institute for Federal Policy Research, G 7 (Box 6)
  - Stanford in Government, G 8 (Box 6)
  - Council on Foreign Relations, G 10 (Box 6)
  - United Nations, G 12 (Box 6)
  - Kaiser, SHS 3 (Box 6)
  - Special / Newco/ UCSF, SHS 3 (Box 6)
  - Stanford Health Care Board of Directors [end 1-31-97; use SHS 15], SHS 3 * UCSF (Box 6)
  - Meeting of the Selectors, SHS 3 *UCSF (Box 6)
  - USHC [UCSF-SU Health Care], SHS 15 (Box 6)
  - UCSF-SHC Merger, UCSF/SHC-1 (Box 6)
  - Hospital Auxillary, SHS 1 (Box 6)
  - Administration - Special File on Dr. Kiran Bhatt, 10/18/99 - 6/29/00; SHS 3 (Box 6)
  - Hospital Administration, SHS 3 (Box 6)
  - Hospital Board of Directors, SHS 4 (Box 6)
  - Lucille Salter Packard Children's Hospital, SHS 7 (Box 6)
  - Medical Organizations (Miscellaneous), SHS 8 (Box 6)
  - Howard Hughes Medical Institute, SHS 9 (Box 6)
  - Other Affiliated Hospitals, Centers and Clinics, SHS 13 (Box 6)
  - Patient Relations, SHS 14 (Box 6)
  - School of Medicine Administration, 2/8/00 - 8/2/00; M 1 (Box 6)
  - School of Medicine Administration, 9/2/99 - 1/24/00 (Box 6)
  - Medical School Development, M 2 (Box 6)
  - Misc. Medical School Departments, M 5 (Box 6)
  - Misc. Ad-Hoc Organizations, 9/9/99 - 8/22/00; O 1 (Box 6)
  - Council of Competitiveness, 11/29/99 - 8/3/00; O 1.2 (Box 6)
  - Stanford Research Institute (SRI), O 2.11 (Box 7)
  - Education Groups, 12/7/99 - 7/17/00; O 3 (Box 7)
  - Education Groups, 9/24/99 - 11/29/99 (Box 7)
  - Consortium on Financing Higher Ed. (COFHE), 9/28/99 - 6/13/00; O 3.1 (Box 7)
  - California Academy of Sciences, 9/7/99 - 7/7/00; O 3.2 (Box 7)
  - Consortium of Social Science Association (COSSA), O 3.3 (Box 7)
  - Association Pacific Rim University, O 3.4 (Box 7)
  - American Adademy of Arts and Sciences, 9/13/99 - 5/30/00; O 3.7 (Box 7)
  - American Council on Education, 9/22/99 - 8/22/00; O 3.8 (Box 7)
  - National Assocation of Independent Colleges & Univ., O 3.10 (Box 7)
  - College Entrance Exam Board, 9/3/99 - 5/9/00; O 3.25 (Box 7)
  - Aspen Institute, O 3.37 (Box 7)
  - Institute of International Education (IIE), O 3.38 (Box 7)
  - National Academy of Sciences (NAS), 6/7/00 - 8/25/00; O 3.43 (Box 7)
  - National Academy of Sciences (NAS), 10/21/99 - 6/1/00 (Box 7)
  - National Academy of Sciences (NAS), 9/15/99 - 10/22/99 (Box 7)
  - National Collegiate Athletic Association (NCAA), 3/23/00 - 8/23/00; O 3.44 (Box 7)
  - National Collegiate Athletic Association (NCAA), 3/31/00 - 3/16/00 (Box 7)
  - National Collegiate Athletic Association (NCAA), 11/22/99 - 3/6/00 (Box 7)
  - National Collegiate Athletic Association (NCAA), 10/4/99 - 11/22/99 (Box 7)
  - Pacific Ten Conference (Pac-10), 3/7/00 - 8/22/00; O 3.47 (Box 8)
  - Pacific Ten Conference (Pac-10), 9/2/99 - 3/1/00 (Box 8)
  - CA Business Higher Education Forum, O 3.56 (Box 8)
  - Athletic Awards Miscellaneous, O 4 (Box 8)
  - Political Groups, Miscellaneous, O 6 (Box 8)
  - Research Organizations, Miscellaneous, O 7 (Box 8)
  - Institute for Civil Injustice - RAND Corporation, O 7.9 (Box 8)
  - University Research Association, 10/29/99 - 3/3/00; O 7.16 (Box 8)
  - Other Colleges and Universities, 6/16/00 - 8/30/00; O 8 (Box 8)
  - Other Colleges and Universities, 6/7/00 - 6/9/00 (Box 8)
  - Other Colleges and Universities, 3/20/00 - 5/24/00 (Box 8)
  - Other Colleges and Universities, 1/7/00 - 3/20/00 (Box 8)
  - Other Colleges and Universities, 9/1/99 - 12/13/99 (Box 8)
  - American Association of Universities, 5/17/00 - 8/18/00; O 8.7 (Box 9)
  - American Association of Universities, 1/4/00 - 5/15/00 (Box 9)
  - American Association of Universities, 9/9/99 - 12/23/99 (Box 9)
  - Assoc. of Governing Boards of Universities & Colleges (AGB), O 8.8 (Box 9)
  - Assoc. of Independent California Colleges & Univ. (AICCU), 9/14/99 - 7/3/00; O 8.9 (Box 9)
  - Cal Tech, O 8.16 (Box 9)
  - California State Universities, O 8.17 (Box 9)
  - Columbia University, O 8.18 (Box 9)
  - Cornell University, O 8.19 (Box 9)
  - Harvard University, O 8.23 (Box 9)
  - Peking University, O 8.30 (Box 9)
  - Princeton University, O 8.36 (Box 9)
  - Nine Provosts, O 8.39 (Box 9)
  - Univ. of CA (All Campuses), 10/7/99 - 5/2/00; O 8.43 (Box 9)
  - University of Chicago, O 8.44 (Box 9)
  - University of Michigan, O 8.45 (Box 9)
  - Brigham Young University, O 8.46 (Box 9)
  - University of Oregon, O 8.47 (Box 9)
  - University of Southern California, O 8.49 (Box 9)
  - Western Association of Schools & Colleges (WASC), O 8.52 (Box 9)
  - Yale University, O 8.53 (Box 9)
  - Inaugurations - other schools, O 8.55 (Box 9)
  - Bay Area Economic Forum, 9/3/99 - 7/27/00; O 11 (Box 9)
  - California Council on Science & Technology, 3/30/99 - 9/13/00; O 12 (Box 9)
  - German American Academic Council Foundation (GAAC), O 14 (Box 9)
  - American Philosophical Society, O 15 (Box 9)
  - German Educational Issues, Gov't Studies, O 17 (Box 9)
  - German Stuff, Misc., O 19 (Box 9)
  - Research Misc., R 0 (Box 9)
  - Sponsored Projects, R 1 (Box 9)
  - Stanford Center for Chicano Research (CSSR), R 1.3 (Box 9)
  - Inst. for Research on Women/Gender (same as CROW), R 1.8 (Box 9)
  - Institute for International Studies (IIS), 9/23/99 - 8/31/00; R 1.12 (Box 9)
  - Bio X Project, R 2 (Box 9)
  - Stanford Leadership Institute, R 7 (Box 9)
  - The Science Coalition, R 8 (Box 9)
  - Students (Misc.), 9/21/99 - 7/25/00; ST 1 (Box 9)
  - Student (Groups), 10/31/99 - 3/31/00; ST 1.1 (Box 9)
  - Ram's Head/Gaeities, ST 1.3 (Box 9)
  - Associated Students of Stanford University (ASSU), ST 2 (Box 9)
  - Stanford Band, ST 3.4 (Box 9)
  - Bechtel International Center, ST 3.5 (Box 9)
  - Hillel, ST 3.7 (Box 9)
  - KZSU, ST 3.18 (Box 9)
  - Haas Public Service Center (T. Stanton), ST 3.29 (Box 9)
  - Gardner, John - Fellowship, ST 3.29/1 (Box 9)
  - Campus Compact, 1/14/00 - 7/26/00; ST 3.35 (Box 9)
  - ASIA-PACIFIC Scholars Program, ST 7.1 (Box 9)
  - Student/Parent Correspondence, 9/13/99 - 8/3/00; ST 8 (Box 9)
- Personnel and search files, 1994-1999; Accession ARCH-2005-285
  The materials are restricted until 2069.
  - PAA 1.8 -Memorial Church Search, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - AD 3.10 -Bryan Chen, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - AD 3.10 -Bryan Chen, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - AD 3.10 -Bryan Chen, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Chronological files, 1992, 1999; Accession ARCH-2005-292
  - 1992 May (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - 1992 Aug (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - 1992 Sep (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - 1992 Oct (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - 1992 Nov (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - 1992 Dec (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - 1999 Jan (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 1999 Feb (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 1999 Mar (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 1999 Apr (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 1999 May (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 1999 Jun (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 1999 Jul (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 1999 Aug (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 1999 Sep (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - 1999 Oct (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - 1999 Nov (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - 1999 Dec (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-2018-040
  - Letters to Parents, Students, and Grad Students, 1993-2000 (Box 1, Folder 1)